Viewers all over the world, thank you very much for your time.
Those of us who are under the influence of this telecast,
wherever you are, whatever situation you are in, listen -
demon is a liar and I want to prove it to you that whatever affliction or trouble you have,
it's behind it.
Right now, begin to remove your hands of affliction,
your hands of disappointment from my people!
Right now, before we call the name Jesus, begin to remove your hand!
You, behind the affliction, disappointment, setback,
right now, I command you to remove your hand, in the name of Jesus!
Your hands of affliction - remove them, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Remove your hands! I command - remove your hands!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see you removing your hands.
Never you again attack my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I warn you, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Never you again attack my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever that pain or affliction is located,
in the mighty name of Jesus, be rebuked!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Your affliction can be sickness, disease, pain, headaches, cancer,
deadly disease in your blood, fluids, or tendons - be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
As you know Jesus' name, be set free!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be set free!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
As you seek God, be fulfilled!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be fulfilled, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Open your lips and begin to confess the name Jesus and the Word of Jesus over your situation.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Dry bones shall rise again! Confess.
His Word does not return to Him without fulfillment.
Confess - over your situation!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to Him for taking you out of the pain.
Give thanks to Him for taking you out of the affliction.
Give thanks to Him for taking you out of sickness and disease.
Give thanks to Him!
As you thank Him, it happens.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I command healing on you!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be healed!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see the light in your bones.
I can see the light in your blood.
I can see the light of God in your faculties.
Light!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen!
I can see the light of God in your organs.
There is light going ---
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Say, "I can see the light".
Say, "I can sense the light".
Say, "I feel the light in my bones".
Say, "I feel the light in my blood".
Say, "Light of God, in my organs".
Say, "Light of God, in my faculties".
Light!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The light of God is to heal you.
The light of God is to deliver you.
The light of God is to free you.
The light of God is to bless you.
The light of God is to save you.
Say, "Light!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever wall between you and God, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be relationship!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
W-A-L-L could be a weakness.
Whatever sin, whatever weakness - whatever wall between you and God, be removed!
Be crumbled!
Let there be relationship!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name.
Say, " There is a relationship between me and my Creator, Jesus Christ!" Confess this.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name